

Hunter Long

Washington, DC 20016 (410) 404-7250 whunterlong@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL () SUMMARY

I am a full stack software engineer with an extensive background in design. My previous experience in art direction and product management gives me insight into areas beyond development. I have a passion for crafting unique products that never lose sight of the end user experience.

SKILLS (

- CSS Editing
- Logo creation
- Corporate Identity Branding
- Adobe Illustrator expert
- Web Design
- Adobe InDesign
- Proficient in Adobe Acrobat
- Complex problem solver

WORK HISTORY

WEB DESIGNER

02/2016 to 03/2017

Colure Media | New York, New York

ART DIRECTOR

03/2017 to CURRENT

Colure Media | New York, New York

- Contributed to creative process through original ideas and inspiration.
- Developed art and design concepts.
- Mentored junior artists on creative processes.
- Learned new software packages in addition to traditional art methods.
- Delivered on multiple titles and platforms simultaneously.
- Designed visual models meeting both aesthetic and technical criteria.

MANAGER

09/2013 to 01/2016

Ups Store | Washington, DC, DC

- Prepared quotes for new products and services and composed budgets.
- Set and managed schedules to give proper coverage to required areas
- and meet customer service demands.
- Hired, trained and mentored staff to maximize effectiveness.

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

01/2014 to CURRENT

Self Employed

EDUCATION \Diamond